- 9818411263
- aasmamnlegmail.com
- Godawari, lalitpur

SRIJANA MAINALI

Junior UI/UX Designer

EDUCATION

Higher Education

Bluebird Secondary School Kumaripati, Lalitpur

2018-2020

Bachelor in Information and Communication Technology

Asia e-University, Virinchi College Kumaripati, Lalitpur

2020-Present (8th Sem)

SKILLS

- UI/UX Design
- Design System
- Communication
- Illustration

TOOLS

- Figma
- Photoshop
- Adobe XD
- HTML/CSS/JS
- Canva
- Slack
- Jira
- Sketch

LANGUAGE

English

Nepali

Hindi

REFERENCES

Roshan Kc

Virinchi College / Academy Coordinator

Phone: 9851191864

Email: roshan.kc@virinchicollege.edu.np

ABOUT ME

Greeting of the day! I am Srijana Mainali, a passionate and dedicated UI/UX designer with a strong drive to use my knowledge in creating meaningful and impactful user experiences. I work hard and with desire, always aiming for excellence in whatever I do.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

Nepali case Study / Godawari, Lalitpur / May, 2022 - December, 2022

Social media handler

TT Byte Nepal / Godawari,lalitpur / January, 2021 - June, 2021

UI/UX Design Instructor

Virinchi College/ Kumaripati ,Lalitpur / Jan, 2023 - Dec, 2023

UI/UX Designer

Mero Ghar / Sadobato ,lalitpur / jan, 2024 - Nov, 2024

TRAINING/CERTIFICATION

Figma

Virinchi College / 2022

Tech to Learn / 2022

Personality Development / 2023

Master-level UI/UX design courses/ 2023

PROJECT

Bus Management System

Children learning App

Super Truck App/Websites

Advik.Ai web Application

Admin Dashboard

MeroGhar Websites design